<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Connor Reardon</title>
    <link>http://www.connorreardon.com.s3-website.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Connor Reardon</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2019 22:32:09 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.connorreardon.com.s3-website.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>FMC Certifications</title>
      <link>http://www.connorreardon.com.s3-website.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/posts/post-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2019 22:32:09 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.connorreardon.com.s3-website.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/posts/post-02/</guid>
      <description>In order to deepen my technical understanding of company finances, I took a financial model bootcamp with Adventis. In the course I learned to build fully circular, three-statement financial models from scratch and practiced the techniques and ideas beyond the bootcamp. I then completed both levels of certifications, showing that I have internalized the modeling techniques as well as concepts of accounting, corporate finance, intrinsic and relative valuation, and leveraged buyout transactions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Deacon Fund</title>
      <link>http://www.connorreardon.com.s3-website.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/posts/post-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2019 22:32:09 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.connorreardon.com.s3-website.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/posts/post-03/</guid>
      <description>The Deacon Fund, of all my extracurriculars, has been the most effective channel of keeping me current and engaged in markets and technology. On a daily basis, the group uses slack to have open conversations on interesting articles and business implications of recent news. Longer term projects include preparing stock proposals, pitching stocks to a panel, raising money for the fund, and following equity under coverage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Decision to Pursue the CFA</title>
      <link>http://www.connorreardon.com.s3-website.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/posts/post-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2019 22:32:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.connorreardon.com.s3-website.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/posts/post-01/</guid>
      <description>I have decided to prepare for the CFA exam in December with the intention of becoming a member of CFA Institute in the long term. I believe the curriculum in my university courses this year and next will lend itself nicely to my success in the first CFA exam. Currently, I am undecided to pursuing a Masters degree and so starting the CFA program is the step I’m taking at the moment to prepare myself for work following next year.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>